# **Adam Japal**

+62(816) 244-614 <u>adam.japal@gmail.com</u> <u>Bandar Lampung, Indonesia</u>

**Senior Software Engineer** I have 3 years' experiences as a programmer at Baturaja Portland Cement (<a href="http://semenbaturaja.co.id">http://semenbaturaja.co.id</a>) and now as a senior software engineer at Institut Teknologi Sumatera (<a href="http://www.itera.ac.id">www.itera.ac.id</a>). I have passionate person and discipline.



### **Key Skills**

- PHP Advance
- Code Igniter Advance
- HTML **Advance**
- MySQL Advance
- Laravel Advance
- CSS Advance
- Angular **Advance**
- Python Advance
- PostgreSQL Advance
- Oracle Database 10g Advance
- Ionic Framework **Advance**
- Node is **Advance**
- Photoshop **Advance**
- Analysis Advance
- Golang Intermediate

### **Experience**

02/2017 - now

## Senior Software Engineer Institut Teknologi Sumatera, Indonesia

Developing and maintenance the whole system in the university

09/2014 to 05/2016

## **Programmer Baturaja Portland Cement,** Indonesia

• Answered customer questions and resolved service

### **Education**

#### **Master of Computer Science:**

Data Science 2019 – now Institute of Informatics and Business Darmajaya, Indonesia

**Bachelor Degree**: Informatics Engineering 2015 Teknokrat University, Indonesia

#### **Hobbies**

- Playing guitar
- Hiking

## **Project Portfolio**

- Multi Dashboard
   Monitoring System at
   Yayasan Al-Kautsar
   Lampung, Indonesia
- Toefl Online Examination at UIN Raden Intan Lampung
- Remax Mobile
   Application at Remax
   Indonesia
- Digital Smart School at PT. Aplikasi Digital Indonesia